so thanks for joining us everybody good
非常感谢大家加入我们
morning or good afternoon depending on
早上或下午好，取决于
which time doing your connecting to this
哪个时间连接到此
webinar from my name is Josh long as I
我的网路研讨会是Josh，只要我
was just so wonderfully introduced I'm
刚刚被介绍得很棒
the developer advocate for the spring
春天的开发商倡导者
projects at at pivotal and pivotal by
在关键点和关键点
the by is the new home of spring it's
by是春天的新家
where the spring team and although great
春季队虽然很棒
open source Apache you know in patchy
您知道的开源Apache
license context and so on moved in April
许可证上下文等在4月移动
of this year it's a new company founded
今年是一家新公司成立
on open source so we're we're the new
在开源上，所以我们是新的
home of spring including RabbitMQ Redis
春季之家，包括RabbitMQ Redis
the Grails project the movie leadership
Grails计划电影领导
apache tomcat leadership you know cloud
你知道Tomcat的Apache领导
trying to the open source platform
尝试开源平台
as-a-service a hadoop distribution and
作为一种Hadoop分发
lots of you know really just a great
你们很多人都知道，真的很棒
open source stack for dealing with
用于处理的开源堆栈
today's problems and building for
今天的问题和建设
tomorrow's needs you know very very very
明天的需求，你知道非常非常非常
forward-thinking we're problem we're
前瞻性思考我们是问题，我们是
facing and of course at the heart of all
面对，当然是所有人的核心
this spring is the sort of component
今年春天是其中的一部分
modeling glue for those of you of you
为您中的那些建模胶水
spring for you know you'll probably know
春天，因为你知道你可能会知道
that there's there can be a lot of
那里可能有很多
different options you know a lot of
您知道很多不同的选择
different choices so to help sort of
不同的选择，以便于帮助
better understand that that field is
更好地了解那个领域是
this diagram here right so the top level
这个图在这里，所以顶层
here is the iowa execution layer this
这是爱荷华州执行层
layer if you look at the diagram that
层，如果你看图
describes are the technologies in the
描述的是
spring stack and help you deal with
弹簧堆栈，并帮助您应对
processes and of course that's a very
过程，当然这是一个非常
low level
低级
you know metaphor or edium but basically
你知道隐喻或乏味，但基本上
spring XD is a turnkey appliance for
spring XD是用于
dealing with large and real-time data
处理大型实时数据
processing solutions and spring moot is
处理解决方案和春天的模拟是
our focusing of attention for spring
我们对春季的关注
applications it's a way of building
应用程序是一种构建方式
applications using convention over
使用约定的应用程序
configuration as far as possible and of
尽可能的配置
course quail's is our Ruby language
鹌鹑是我们的Ruby语言
rapid application web framework that
快速应用程序网络框架
needs no introduction and all of these
不需要介绍，所有这些
technologies sit on top of the rich sort
技术位于富人之上
of wealth of ABI API and libraries that
丰富的ABI API和库
spring provides including support for
春天提供包括支持
integration batch processing the data
集成批处理数据
web applications reactive or otherwise
Web应用程序反应性或其他
and of course all that interns it's on
当然，所有实习生都在
top of our common data support for no
通用数据支持的顶部
sequel new sequel not only sequel and
续集新续集不仅续集和
sequel date data stores and then all
续集日期数据存储，然后全部
that further sits on top of things like
进一步位于诸如
the core framework and you know it can
核心框架，您知道它可以
work with common things like a spring
与春天一样的普通事物一起工作
security so you know when you see
安全性，让您知道何时看到
pivotal out there it's still us we're
关键在那里我们仍然是我们
still still the same team and we just
仍然是同一支球队，我们只是
and we have a new home on the web by the
我们在网上有了一个新家
way we're actually now at a spring that
实际上我们现在正处于春天
i/o so if you go to SpringSource better
I / O，所以如果您更好地去SpringSource
org you'll be redirected to spring that
org，您将被重定向到spring那
i/o there you'll find lots of great
在这里，您会发现很多很棒的东西
getting started guides that take about
入门指南
10 to 15 minutes to complete to to you
10至15分钟即可完成
know just is he completed you follow the
知道他完成了吗？
guides and you can see every step of the
指南，您可以看到
way required to achieve a certain task
完成某项任务所需的方式
so if you wanted if you were let's see
所以如果你想的话让我们看看
course it's important that you have a
当然，拥有一个
browser so you can go here you can see
浏览器，以便您可以在这里看到
there's access to the guides the
可以访问指南
projects of blogs etc this application
博客项目等此应用程序
is itself a spring application it runs
它本身就是运行的spring应用程序
on top of Cloud Foundry so and that will
在Cloud Foundry之上
itself be open sourced a little bit
本身是开源的
later so looking forward a little bit
以后再期待一点
you know spring for it's just around the
你知道春天就在附近
corner to be within I believe we're
我相信我们在
saying it's the 12th of this month
说这是本月十二号
actually we're have it available so you
实际上我们有可用的，所以您
can expect to see that very very soon
可以期待很快看到
and spring for as all springs before it
一生的春天
have been is very much a framework for
一直是一个框架
the JVM it's not just a Java language
JVM不仅是Java语言
specific framework and what this means
具体框架及其含义
in practice is that we have good support
实际上是我们有很好的支持
for different versions of the Java of
适用于不同版本的Java
course and you know alternative support
当然，您知道替代支持
where appropriate people think that you
适当的人认为你
need to use xml to configure beans and
需要使用xml来配置bean和
spring and this just not so input in
春天，这不是那么输入
fact you have it needed to use it for a
事实上，您需要将其用于
long time you can do things entirely
很长一段时间你可以完全做事
inside of java or you can use groovy or
在Java内部，也可以使用groovy或
scala or what have you
斯卡拉或你有什么
spring doesn't care where you where i
春天不在乎你在哪里我
get to get the information about which
获得有关哪个的信息
cloud
云
is you having an application and how
您有应用程序吗？
they need to get wired up together etc
他们需要连接在一起等等
as long as you do provide it right so we
只要您提供正确，我们
provided different API use to help you
提供了不同的API使用来帮助您
can you know explain the stuff to spring
你能解释春天的东西吗
so for example if you're using the
因此，例如，如果您使用的是
spring scholar project again just calls
春季学者项目再次呼吁
a nice language to use inside of
在内部使用的好语言
IntelliJ so there's no reason you
IntelliJ所以没有理由你
couldn't they're using the spring Scala
他们不能使用春季Scala
project then you could use the
项目，那么您可以使用
functional configuration API here you
功能配置API在这里你
can see we're defining different means
可以看到我们正在定义不同的方法
using a DSL taking advantage of some of
利用DSL的优势
the dynamic features of the scholar
学者的动态特征
language we could also use a groovy beam
语言，我们也可以使用Groovy Beam
builder this is of course has been
建设者，这当然是
around for a long time inside of the
在里面很长一段时间
Grails project and inside of the spring
谷物突出并在弹簧内部
for will see it merged into the core GUI
对于它将看到它合并到核心GUI
bean Builder of course again uses the
Bean Builder当然会再次使用
DSL that's provided by the GUI language
GUI语言提供的DSL
which is another technology works very
这是另一项非常有效的技术
nicely inside of IntelliJ and of course
很好地在IntelliJ内部
Java to have a configuration so this
Java具有配置，因此
style has been around since we
自从我们出现风格以来
introduced the spring Java config
引入了春季Java配置
project in 2000 and what is it 4 or 5
2000年的项目，它是4还是5
and then that support get merged into
然后将支持合并到
the core in 2009 and so here we have a
2009年的核心，所以在这里我们有一个
class which has a reconfiguration
具有重新配置的类
annotation and each bean is the
注释，每个bean是
basically the description each pin
基本上每个引脚的描述
method at beam method is the equivalent
光束法等于
of the bean tag in XML
XML中的bean标签
the return value becomes that for class
返回值变为类的返回值
and then of course any bean idea can be
当然，任何豆子的想法都可以
specified in the bean annotation or the
在bean注释或
method name itself can be can be used to
方法名称本身可以用来
derive a bean ID so yeah there's lots of
派生一个bean ID，是的，有很多
different ways to configure your
不同的方式来配置您的
application and of course with things
应用，当然还有东西
like spring boot which we'll look at it
就像 spring boot ，我们来看看
in a little bit there's often very
有时候，通常
little need to do even this kind of kind
甚至不需要做这种事情
of configuration at all um Java 8 it's
所有um Java 8的配置
of course a very very interesting
当然非常非常有趣
destination for swing applications it
摇摆应用的目的地
has a lot of great features things I'm
我有很多很棒的功能
really excited to see finally in the
真的很高兴终于看到
platform as I'm sure most of you are as
平台，因为我敢肯定你们大多数人
well one of those features of course is
当然，这些功能之一是
lambdas you know and this is something
你知道的lambdas，这是东西
that I think a lot of us in the
我认为我们很多人
community have been waiting for it's a
社区一直在等待
little awkward that in
有点尴尬
C++ commedia language was governing body
C ++ commedia语言是领导机构
meats but once or twice a year if that
肉，但每年一次或两次
sometimes even they have lambdas already
有时甚至他们已经有了lambda
and we don't so I think it would be very
而且我们不这样做，我认为那将是非常
very good to finally get this support
最终获得此支持非常好
last I heard the support let's do some
最后我听到了支持，让我们做一些
you know first quarter next year
你知道明年第一季度
that might slip a little bit but I way
可能会有点滑但我这样
it's imminent so I'm excited
迫在眉睫，我很兴奋
and of course IntelliJ has had great
当然IntelliJ也有很棒的
support for Java 8 for more than a year
对Java 8的支持超过一年
which is another reason why you there's
这是你在那里的另一个原因
no reason to be afraid to get start with
没有理由害怕开始
this stuff now one thing that I really
这东西现在是我真正的一件事
you know Lam does go hand in hand with
你知道林的确与
another feature that I like and which is
我喜欢的另一个功能是
the method referenced syntax here I've
该方法在这里引用了语法
got a typical JDBC template example I'm
我有一个典型的JDBC模板示例
issuing a query and I'm passing a you
发出查询，而我通过
know the second argument there is an
知道第二个论点有一个
instance of Springs row mapper row
Springs行映射器行的实例
mapper is an interface that has just one
映射器是只有一个接口
method this is called a functional
方法，称为功能
interface inside of Java 8 and
Java 8和
functional interfaces can be substituted
功能接口可以替代
for method references that provide the
对于提供
same return value in the same method
相同方法的相同返回值
arguments it doesn't matter what the
论点无关紧要
name of the method itself is of course
方法本身的名称当然是
so here instead of a row map or
所以这里而不是行图或
anonymous class I can just return a I
我可以返回一个匿名类
can just provide a reference to just a
只能提供一个参考
map method which is very convenient you
地图方法，这很方便
know this is a great thing to make it
知道做到这一点很棒
even more concise to make it even
更加简明扼要
cleaner you can use a in-line lambdas or
清洁剂，您可以使用内联Lambda或
no sort of anonymous Landis this has the
没有那种匿名的兰迪斯
benefit of not only being very concise
不仅非常简洁的好处
but for the first time and I think
但是这是我第一次
history we have tweetable Enterprise
我们有推文的历史企业
Java code which is a very very good
Java代码非常好
thing so here I'm actually using the
东西，所以在这里我实际上正在使用
same jpz template but using this very
相同的jpz模板，但是非常使用
very concise notation for creating a
创建一个非常简洁的符号
function reference you know same idea
功能参考，你知道相同的想法
for something basically creating an
对于基本上创建一个
interface at from you know at runtime
您在运行时知道的界面
and code it looks so much much more
并编码它看起来要多得多
concise other features like the J's
简洁的其他功能，例如J
far-left J's are 3/10 support is
最左端的J是3/10支持
basically a Steven Colburn's and
基本上是史蒂文·科尔本（Steven Colburn）和
joda-time API are now part of JDK 8 and
joda-time API现在是JDK 8和
of course this support is this support
当然，这种支持就是这种支持
propagates all the way through the
一直传播到
spring so you can actually use Springs
春天，所以你实际上可以使用春天
binding and validation support wherever
绑定和验证支持在任何地方
probe
探测
with j7 3 10 other nice features like
与j7 3 10其他不错的功能，如
repeatable annotations inside of dog and
狗和里面的可重复注释
H are also supported inside of spring
H也支撑在弹簧内部
were appropriate of course in the
当然是适当的
discussion of spring 4 would be
春季4的讨论将是
incomplete without talking about the
不谈不完的
continuing continually improved rest
持续不断地改善休息
support nicety this is not a huge
支持尼斯这不是很大
feature but it's a very convenient
功能，但非常方便
little thing is this a tres controller
小事情是这个tres控制器
annotation is syntax sugar for app
注释是应用程序的语法糖
controller and then lets you drop off
控制器，然后让您下车
the response body for each you know
您认识的每个人的回应主体
method so while this doesn't do anything
方法，虽然这不会做任何事情
you couldn't technically do in previous
您以前在技术上无法做到
versions of spring for many years it
春天的版本很多年了
does reduce the sort of notational
确实减少了符号的种类
complexity quite a bit just because you
相当多的复杂性只是因为你
get to remove an annotation for method
获得删除方法的注释
so that's very nice and the one thing
所以这很好，一件事
i'm you know a lot of people are looking
我你知道很多人在找
forward to inside of spring for is of
前进到春天的里面
course our WebSocket support so of
当然我们的W​​ebSocket支持如此
course spring for supports jace are
当然支持杰斯的春天是
three five six but we've also got
三五六，但我们也有
improved support to support a couple of
改进了支持以支持几个
use cases that the jsr by itself don't
jsr本身不使用的用例
meet so first of all them web sockets
首先见面网络插座
while nice aren't universally available
虽然不错，但并非普遍可用
in browsers and so we need some sort
在浏览器中，所以我们需要某种
fallback option again it's I wouldn't
后备选项再次是我不会
want to name names or point fingers but
想命名名字或食指，但是
some browsers are maybe a little bit
一些浏览器可能有点
slow to implement this or you know they
实施起来很慢，或者你知道他们
they have valiantly implemented but up
他们英勇地执行了
until say a version ten they didn't have
直到说出他们没有的第十版
complete support for it again I won't
完全支持它，我不会
name names but I guess you I suspect you
名字，但我想你我怀疑你
guys can probably guess which browser
伙计们可能会猜出哪个浏览器
that is so you know you want a fallback
这样您就知道要回退
option that's oh that's an important
哦，这很重要
part of building modern web applications
构建现代Web应用程序的一部分
and then in additionally in addition the
然后另外
days are is a it is two web sockets what
天是一个它是两个Web套接字什么
servlets are two HTTP endpoints it works
servlet是它起作用的两个HTTP端点
but basically if you want to do any kind
但基本上，如果您想做任何事情
of routing you end up funneling
路由最终导致您进入渠道
everything through a central Handler and
一切都通过中央处理程序
then doing an if-then-else check
然后做一个if-then-else检查
so map rating based on the destination
因此根据目的地进行地图评分
of your messages isn't natural in this
您的消息不自然
case because you wind up funnelling to
情况是因为您最终集中到
this warning signal handler you need
您需要的这个警告信号处理程序
some sort of controller after all right
毕竟可以使用某种控制器
so both of these things we've addressed
所以我们都解决了这两个问题
with with our support we've actually got
在我们的支持下，我们实际上已经
support for SATA jeaious which is a
支持SATA jeaious，这是一个
superset of WebSocket protocol so you
WebSocket协议的超集，因此您
can use that with the stock to disk
可以将其与库存一起使用
client and get graceful degradation of
客户并得到优雅的降级
you know the the bi-directional channel
你知道双向通道
across different browsers even though
即使跨不同的浏览器
that don't support WebSockets natively
本机不支持WebSockets
and of course spring 4 supports the
当然，弹簧4支持
stomp protocol which is modeled after
踏板协议
htb frames and we support it on top of
htb框架，我们支持它
WebSockets this is something you can use
WebSockets这是您可以使用的东西
you can also plug into a book like
你也可以像
RabbitMQ or ActiveMQ so you don't have
RabbitMQ或ActiveMQ，因此您无需
to you know you can use the simple brook
你知道你可以用简单的小溪
for that you set up inside of the spring
因为你在春天里面建立了
MVC or you can use one that plugs into
MVC或您可以使用一种插入
something else like that like a rabbit
像兔子一样的东西
and a few brokers this gives you a
和一些经纪人，这给你一个
messaging protocol and in this way you
通讯协议，通过这种方式，您
can take advantage of messaging spousal
可以利用消息传递的配偶
antics there's not very reactive web
滑稽动作没有很活跃的网络
applications here's an example of an
应用程序是一个示例
endpoint inside of a controller that
控制器内部的端点
will receive a message and then you know
将收到一条消息，然后您知道
handle it and afford it to the lead and
处理它，并把它负担给领导和
the topic that you know we're under the
您所知道的主题是
messages it's sent out to anime who's
它发送给动漫的消息
missing on topic for such greetings so
缺少关于此类问候的话题，所以
it has to just come in and for such
它必须只是进来，为此
creating from a client and they get
从客户创建，他们得到
routed to topic for slash greetings
路由到主题进行斜线问候
there's another there's another
还有另一个还有另一个
important type called a subscribe event
重要类型称为订阅事件
at act subscribe event and that gives
在行动订阅事件，这给
you the chance to send back MedCity to
您有机会将MedCity发送回
the client where that without routing
没有路由的客户端
through the broker immediately so let's
通过经纪人，所以让我们
even handle the subscription event for
甚至处理以下订阅事件
first off and this is a very natural you
首先，这是很自然的你
know component model for building
知道建筑的组件模型
applications routing in this case of
在这种情况下的应用程序路由
course is based on the destination
当然是根据目的地
header of the message so at the bat
消息的标题，所以在蝙蝠
message mapping for such greeting this
消息映射为此问候
will feel very simple similar to at
会感觉很像at
request mapping it's kind of spring MVC
请求映射，这是一种Spring MVC
confirming such a continuing such
确认这样的继续
WebSocket support of course is fairly
WebSocket支持当然是相当
straightforward here's an example of a
简单明了，这是一个例子
configuration class and we
配置类，我们
turn on it would suck it the simple
打开它会很简单
WebSocket message broker support here
WebSocket消息代理支持在这里
turning it on for you know a portfolio
打开它，因为你知道一个投资组合
project and above this you know beyond
项目，除此之外，您还知道
answers of course lots of great features
当然有很多很棒的功能的答案
as well but I just wanted to give you
我也想给你
kind of the broad strokes of course Java
Java的种种招式
EE 7 is very well supported inside of a
EE 7在一个
spring for the new daytime it we already
春天已经到了新的白天，我们已经
looked at the day time API but in
看了白天的API，但是
addition to that the bean validation and
除了bean的验证和
concurrent API is the new servlet and
并发API是新的servlet，
Sheamus and JTA cuts are supported and
支持Sheamus和JTA剪切
as I just described the JCR 356 is well
正如我刚刚描述的，JCR 356很好
supported and even the batch chase R
支持甚至批量追逐R
which we actually had a hand in helping
实际上我们有帮助
to craft is of course I love supporting
我当然喜欢手工
so on you know we're very happy to
所以您知道我们很高兴
support Java there's a lot of love out
支持Java，有很多的爱
there I hope you guys will you know
在那里，我希望你们会知道
check out the release photos that are
查看发布的照片
being made available so with that yeah
被提供，所以是的
did you want to resume Josh yes
你想恢复乔希吗
just for this noised introduction any
只是为了这个喧闹的介绍
questions up there or shall we just
问题在那里，还是我们只是
continue now okay so my screen okay so
现在继续，好吧，我的屏幕好吧，所以
my name is Yun Seong I am one of the
我叫润成我是
spring developers in IntelliJ IDEA team
IntelliJ IDEA团队的Spring开发人员
and while today we will focus on what's
而今天，我们将专注于
new in IntelliJ 13 I quickly also want
我很快也想要IntelliJ 13的新功能
to talk about some basic concepts so
说说一些基本概念
that everybody maybe who is not very
每个人也许不是很
familiar with south support and IntelliJ
熟悉南方支持和IntelliJ
works can understand what we are doing
作品可以了解我们在做什么
here
这里
so in IntelliJ we have modules which
所以在IntelliJ中，我们有一些模块
combine certain related functionality
结合某些相关功能
and modules can have facets and we have
和模块可以有多个方面，我们有
here a spring facet which needs to be
这里的弹簧面需要
added to one module and they have the
添加到一个模块，他们有
concept of facets which more or less
构面的概念或多或少
resemble application contacts so you can
类似于应用程序联系人，因此您可以
actually remodel your application
实际重塑您的应用程序
context or multiple application contacts
上下文或多个应用程序联系人
as you configure them a new application
当您配置他们一个新的应用程序
in this spring facet so IntelliJ IDEA
在这个春季，IntelliJ IDEA
will understand how the relationship
会了解如何建立关系
between configuration files or Java
在配置文件或Java之间
configuration works to get us or
配置可以使我们或
resolving and navigation and all this
解析和导航以及所有这些
IDE functionality works as expected
IDE功能按预期工作
ok so much for a very quick introduction
很好，可以非常快速地进行介绍
into spring because it's very important
进入春天，因为这非常重要
to get right and we'll come back to that
正确，我们将回到这一点
issue later when we show some new stuff
稍后发布，当我们展示一些新东西时
in this area yes as just-just-just said
在这方面，正如刚才所说
spring for all has very tight
所有人的春天都非常紧张
integration with Java EE 7 which is also
与Java EE 7集成
one very big area in IntelliJ 13 which
IntelliJ 13中有一个很大的区域
and enhance a lot so we already support
并增强很多，所以我们已经支持
all the new specifications from until
从直到的所有新规格
from Java EE 7 we also have support for
从Java EE 7开始，我们还支持
the new batch specification for example
例如新的批次规范
so everything is already there to try
所以一切都已经可以尝试了
out if you want to okay
如果你想的话出去
I've prepared a small fake project which
我准备了一个小假项目
is very simplistic in some aspects but
在某些方面非常简单，但是
it's I think good way to show of new
我认为这是展示新事物的好方法
features without introducing too much of
功能而不会引入太多
code so the first issue I want to talk
代码，所以我想谈的第一个问题
about today as being documentation so
今天是作为文档，所以
you all know about the possibility to
你们都知道
invoke quick documentation for code
调用代码快速文档
which is now a feature which also works
现在是一项功能，也可以使用
on spring beans so if my cursor is now
在春豆上，所以如果我的光标现在
located on a spring bean reference like
位于像这样的Spring bean参考上
it is right now I can use the shortcut
现在可以使用快捷方式
to show quick documentation and it will
显示快速文档，它将
show me the name the type of the spring
给我看看弹簧的类型
beam and the location this also works if
梁和位置，如果
your spring bean has some nested
你的春豆有一些嵌套
description tag it will include this
说明标签将包含此标签
documentation as well so I think that's
文档，所以我认为这是
very handy if you need to quickly look
如果您需要快速查看，非常方便
up any beam or want to know more about
或想了解更多有关
it
它
something that works together with the
与
new documentation or what we just saw
新文档或我们刚刚看到的内容
was the type of spring being a small
春天的类型是小的
just plate and the documentation and
只是板和文件
this type is now also more clever with
这种类型现在也更聪明
regard to special being so we have a
关于特殊的存在，所以我们有一个
neutral constant beam and you will read
中性恒定光束，您将阅读
two spring constant for the type of the
两个弹簧常数
spring beam we have extended this to
弹簧梁，我们已经扩展到
most if not all known standard beams in
大部分（如果不是全部）已知的标准光束
spring namespaces we support so spring
我们支持的Spring命名空间
that of course also detected as well as
当然也可以检测到
a task scheduler and you can also
一个任务计划程序，您还可以
navigate to any
导航到任何
Java class right from here so that's
Java类就从这里开始
very convenient if you want to look up
如果你想抬头很方便
something very quickly another thing
很快，另一件事
which is a bit related to that is the
与此有关的是
presentation which has been enhanced in
演示文稿已在
IntelliJ 13 so we have no the in icon
IntelliJ 13因此我们没有in图标
which will change depending on the beam
随光束而变化
type so here we have an abstract beam
键入，所以这里有一个抽象光束
and this abstract beam has a small
这个抽象光束有一个小
difference in the icon so you can
图标上的差异，以便您可以
recognize it visually very easily to say
视觉上很容易辨认
and it's true for prototype beans which
对于原型豆来说，
have this small M on the icon and
在图标上有这个小M
everywhere in the user interface these
这些用户界面中的所有位置
icons will be used so it's very easy to
图标将被使用，因此非常容易
catch different kinds of pins so
抓住不同种类的别针
sometimes you want to use one of the
有时您想使用
refactorings in Springer's law and we
施普林格定律的重构，我们
had long-standing requests for more
长期以来要求更多
intelligence with the renaming beans so
重命名豆的智慧
I'm going to rename this pin right now
我现在要重命名此图钉
and in IntelliJ 13 we have introduced
在IntelliJ 13中，我们引入了
completion for renaming beans so what
重命名豆完成，那么
will compete or show proposals according
将根据以下内容竞争或显示提案
to the class type of the bean and if I
到豆的类类型，如果我
choose a bean ID which is already used
选择一个已经使用过的bean ID
it will also show me an error as well as
它也会显示一个错误以及
the corresponding location of the bean
豆的对应位置
so you can't introduce aiming errors by
因此您不能通过以下方式引入瞄准误差
accident
事故
so the next feature I want to talk about
所以我要谈的下一个功能
is injection we've had a language
是注射，我们有一种语言
injection for a long time in IntelliJ
IntelliJ中长时间注入
IDEA
理念
provided by the entire length plug-in
由全长插件提供
which allows you to inject languages to
这允许您将语言注入
for example strings or XML attributes or
例如字符串或XML属性或
values and this has been extended
值，并且已扩展
through reference as well so you can now
通过参考，所以您现在可以
use it also for spring resource
也可用于春季资源
references as well as for spring mean
参考以及春季平均值
references and I have this small example
参考，我有这个小例子
which is custom wrapping context which
这是自定义包装上下文
for example could be located in your own
例如可以位于您自己的位置
project which some witch reps a real
一些女巫代表真实的项目
application context behind it and let's
它背后的应用程序上下文，让我们
look what we can do with reference
看看我们可以做些什么
injection so here we have the
注射，所以我们在这里
construction of our context and we
构建我们的环境，我们
passed in as parameters the locations of
作为参数传递的位置
the configuration files and I can now
配置文件，我现在可以
use the intention to inject a language
用意图注入语言
of reference and I will inject the new
参考，我将注入新的
reference type spring resource path and
参考类型的弹簧资源路径和
then IntelliJ will understand that the
则IntelliJ将了解
string is now a reference to a spring
字符串现在是对弹簧的引用
resource or it understands the class
资源或它了解课程
pass prefix as well as Tiare prefixes
通过前缀以及Tiare前缀
which are known from spring resource
从春季资源中得知
type so that's very useful if you have
键入，如果有的话这非常有用
or if you want to use the spring
或者如果您想使用弹簧
resource type in any location the next
下一个位置的资源类型
ref
参考
we have it's for spring means so let's
我们有春天的意思，所以让我们
say my reading context has a method to
说我的阅读环境有一种方法
find a beam by its ID usually you would
通常通过其ID查找光束
have no auto completion or at least not
没有自动完成或至少没有
a very useful or a completion in this
一个非常有用的或完成的
context
语境
so let's uncheck the reference to spring
所以我们取消对spring的引用
beam name in this method and now you
这种方法的梁名称，现在您
will have to your auto completion you
将需要您自动完成
already know from spring mix and
已经从春季搭配中知道了
aromatic or Java config files and of
芳香文件或Java配置文件以及
course as always navigation works as
一如既往的导航功能
well as anything else which is available
以及其他任何可用的东西
for spring being references so the last
因为春天是参考，所以最后
injection I want to show very quickly
我想快速显示注射
which has been available before 13 but
已于13年前推出，但
maybe it's not known to many people so
也许很多人不知道
if you have some kind of il expression
如果您有某种il表达式
maybe spring it all or just plain here
也许春天全部到这里或只是在这里
you can as well use this here so we will
您也可以在这里使用它，所以我们将
just tell that or method to resolve
只是告诉或解决的方法
spring is PL expression expects traffic
春天是PL表达期待交通
al a spring al expression and now you
一个春天的表情，现在你
see the highlighting has changed so it
看到突出显示已更改，因此
will even resolve al variables and you
甚至可以解析所有变量，而您
have auto completion that's were here in
具有自动完成功能
your spring al expression okay
你春天的表情还好
topic is about configurations so I
主题是关于配置的，所以我
showed you in the beginning the spring
在春季开始时向您展示
facet which is needed to configure
需要配置的方面
spring application context in Europe
欧洲的春季应用程序上下文
project and what we have added is
项目，我们添加的是
additional checks on project robot which
对项目机器人的其他检查
will guide you to setting up your spring
会指导您设置弹簧
context so to demonstrate this I'm just
上下文，以便证明这一点，我只是
going to close this project and reopen
将要关闭该项目并重新打开
it and we have this notification here on
它，我们在这里有此通知
the right upper corner which tells us
右上角告诉我们
that some unconvicted spring
那些没有定罪的春天
configuration files have been found in
在以下位置找到配置文件
this project so we can actually show
这个项目，所以我们可以实际显示
them right for me and these we're of
他们适合我，而我们
course set up by me so that we have some
我设置的课程，以便我们有一些
bad configuration in this project you
您在此项目中的配置不正确
can as well open the spring facet in the
也可以在其中打开弹簧面
corresponding module and it will also
相应的模块，它也会
repeat this error in the spring facade
在Spring Facade中重复此错误
so you cannot miss anything in your
这样您就不会错过任何东西
module and of course if I edit the
模块，当然，如果我编辑
context here the error will go away
上下文在这里错误会消失
because normally application is properly
因为通常应用程序正确
configured there's a separate entry here
配置这里有一个单独的条目
for programmatic contacts found this is
对于程序化联系人，发现这是
something which is not released and
没有释放的东西
working yet but we are working on it so
还在工作，但是我们正在努力
what's a programmatic context some
什么是程序化上下文
people use programmatic context setups
人们使用程序化上下文设置
for the applications maybe for
对于可能的应用
standalone or command line application
独立或命令行应用程序
for example orders for convenience so
例如为了方便订购
here we instantiate a class parse XML
在这里我们实例化一个类解析XML
application contracts from spring and
春季和春季的申请合同
IntelliJ is highlighting now the usage
IntelliJ现在突出显示用法
of such a programmatic context
这样的程序环境
just going to close the simplification
只是要结束简化
and I can now use the intention to set
现在我可以用这个意图来设定
up this stream context it's problematic
在这个流上下文中有问题
context and it will set up the context
上下文，它将建立上下文
in the Springfest for me what it does
在Springfest对我有什么作用
not do yet and which is the thing which
还没有做，那是什么
is missing which will be relived and
丢失了，将重生
13.1 is gathering all the information
13.1正在收集所有信息
about the programmatic set up and all
关于程序化设置以及所有
configuring this context for you a new
为您配置新的上下文
spring facet so that's very easy also to
春天方面，所以也很容易
depict and set up such contexts
描绘并建立这样的环境
correctly in your IDE
在您的IDE中正确
ok as I said it's just a teaser and that
好的，就像我说的只是一个预告片
programmatic context attention detection
程序性上下文注意检测
is coming and 13.1 what I didn't show
来了13.1我没显示
you was how to suppress for example such
你是如何压制例如
wines so let's remove this Java
葡萄酒，所以让我们删除这个Java
configuration again to make it wrong and
再次配置以使其错误并
immediately it will show a warning also
立即它也会显示警告
in the editor so you will also see
在编辑器中，因此您还将看到
configuration editors configuration
配置编辑器配置
errors in your editor as you type or as
您输入或输入时编辑器中的错误
you change your code and of course you
你改变你的代码，当然你
also have quick fixes here to set up an
也可以在此处快速修复以设置
application context and you can choose
应用程序上下文，您可以选择
any existing application context right
任何现有的应用程序上下文权限
from here and it will add this
从这里，它将添加此
configuration file to the existing
配置文件到现有
context but you can also create a new
上下文，但您也可以创建一个新的
application context as you like it
您喜欢的应用程序上下文
depends of course on your application ok
当然取决于您的应用程序
that's about the configuration changes
关于配置更改
and
和
yeah what it's very new of course is
是的，这当然是很新的
also the detection of unconfigured Java
还可以检测未配置的Java
configuration file code configuration
配置文件代码配置
files we always had detection and
我们一直检测到的文件
highlighting for unconfigured XML files
突出显示未配置的XML文件
so also now your code configuration
所以现在您的代码配置
files will be checked for proper
文件将被检查是否正确
configuration and yeah the focus on
是的，重点是
annotation based configures my keyboard
基于注释的配置我的键盘
to hand over to Josh again we will show
再次交给乔希，我们将展示
some stuff out put some live coding
一些东西放了一些实时编码
which heavily in ever Sanitation base
大量的卫生设施
conflict yeah alright so I wanted to
冲突是的，所以我想
show you guys what it looks like to
向大家展示它的外观
create a brand new application from
从创建一个全新的应用程序
scratch and to get the job done as
从头开始并完成工作
quickly as possible
尽快
I mentioned earlier this spring that I a
我在今年春天早些时候提到我
website you can go to those guides that
网站，您可以去那些指南，
I mentioned and each one of those is
我提到过，每个都是
backed by git repository and you can of
由git仓库支持，您可以
course follow the git repositories to
当然遵循git仓库
get working examples of different things
得到不同事物的工作实例
but another Avenue is just you know
但是你知道另一个大道
piece it together using spring boot
用弹簧靴拼凑起来
spring Buddha's as I mentioned a way of
我提到的春天佛陀的一种
building applications that focuses
构建关注的应用程序
attention on that what you're trying to
注意您要尝试的
do and sort of does anything else by
做和做其他事情
convention wherever possible
尽可能的约定
spring will you know spring has always
春天你会知道春天一直
had conventions so long as you check the
只要您检查
boxes cheek so here we're checking the
盒子脸颊，所以我们在这里检查
boxes for you by looking at your your
看你的盒子给你
application context we're looking at the
我们正在查看的应用程序上下文
class path and wherever possible we do
上课的路，我们尽可能
things for you swimming there aren't
你游泳的东西没有
reasons not to and those reasons might
原因不去，那些原因可能
be for example beans that you know we
例如，您知道我们的豆子
don't need to provide because you've
不需要提供，因为您已经
already provided one yourself and in
已经自己提供了
these examples we you know our support
这些例子，我们知道我们的支持
won't back off and all not you know try
不会退缩，所有不知道的尝试
and do something for you but really your
为你做点事，但实际上是你的
if you have something on the class path
如果您在课程路径上有什么东西
for example then you don't have to opt
例如，那么您不必选择
out of having to have support and that's
不必获得支持，那就是
that's a nice critical there's always
这是一个很好的关键，总是
going to do is add things to your class
要做的就是将内容添加到您的课程中
path and you get more features and you
路径，您将获得更多功能，而您
can tailor them but the customization is
可以定制它们，但是定制是
it's minimal a great way to get started
这是最小的入门方法
with spring boot is to use this little
spring boot 就是用这个小
web service you could have start that
Web服务，您可能已经开始
spring that I oh I'm gonna say org that
春天，我哦，我要说的是
you know courage a and just win you know
你知道勇气，只是赢得你知道
demo of course that is actually what
演示当然就是
this is so there we go we're gonna say
这就是我们要说的
we want the web support right so this
我们想要正确的网络支持，所以这
will bring that this is gonna generate a
将带来这将产生一个
maven project for us that has all those
为我们准备的具有所有这些功能的Maven项目
prepackaged web support one we're gonna
预包装的网络支持，我们将
go ahead and choose them JP a support
继续选择他们JP支持
and we're just gonna go ahead and
我们将继续前进，
generate a maven project like so
像这样生成一个Maven项目
download go to the finder
下载转到取景器
there's our application I've of course
我当然有我们的应用程序
you know fearing the demo gods like I do
你知道像我一样害怕演示神
I've always got a backup but just in
我总是有一个备份，但只是
case we're gonna go ahead and run
如果我们要继续运行
through this and live quarters own
通过这个和自己的住所
something interesting something you know
一些有趣的事情，你知道的
powerful very very quickly so this is
非常非常强大，所以这是
the old one go ahead and start again
旧的继续前进并重新开始
starter then I'll go ahead and just open
入门，然后我继续打开
a regular maven project I had something
我有一个常规的Maven项目
go ahead and choose on the next ml which
继续选择下一个毫升
I'd like to open the project absolutely
我想绝对打开项目
new window please and of course this
请打开新窗口，当然这
launches us into IntelliJ where we were
使我们进入IntelliJ
confronted with a fairly Spartan project
面对一个相当斯巴达的项目
you've got a prebuilt test which does
你有一个预建的测试
next to nothing basically and a code
基本没有什么和代码
what is going on
到底是怎么回事
I have angered something here I just I
我在这里激怒了我
guess big scale fire is broken it's 10%
猜猜大火是10％
sorry
抱歉
fire is broken here oh yes my fault and
火在这里被打破哦，是的，我的错，
so I won't service needs to be fixed any
所以我不需要维修任何
water important absolutely yes good so
水很重要，绝对是，所以很好
lesson there is don't put ampersand in
上课不要放“＆”号
your generated output thank you for that
您生成的输出感谢您
good catch
接得好
okay we have a very Spartan directory
好吧，我们有一个非常斯巴达的目录
structure we have a public static void
我们有一个公共静态结构
main you know inside of a class and it's
主要你在一堂课里面知道的
the at table auto-configuration
at表自动配置
this is bring boots cue telling it to do
这是把靴子提示告诉它要做的
whatever it can for us on on our behalf
代表我们为我们做的一切
based on convention remember we've
根据惯例，记得我们已经
chosen to have the spring boot start up
选择启动弹簧靴
web and we want the actuator and 1jp
网络，我们想要执行器和1jp
support as well as testing support but
支持和测试支持，但
more on that for now and what this gets
现在更多，这会得到什么
you is all the libraries you're gonna
你就是你要去的所有图书馆
likely need to do web applications and
可能需要做Web应用程序和
all the libraries are gonna like the
所有的图书馆都会像
need to do JPA database applications so
需要做JPA数据库应用程序
this is an opinionated you know we're
这是一个自以为是的事，你知道我们
gonna do everything we can to be useful
会竭尽所能
at the box sort of thing let's go ahead
在盒子里，让我们继续吧
and build it just a simple application
并构建一个简单的应用程序
and we'll start using the default
我们将开始使用默认值
approach which is public static void
公共静态无效的方法
main we're gonna actually build a web
主要我们实际上要建立一个网站
application but you can still leave it
申请，但您仍然可以离开
like this or we can convert it into a
这样，或者我们可以将其转换为
war we'll do that in a little bit so
战争，我们会这样做一点
let's just imagine a fictitious some
让我们想象一个虚拟的
sort of database of booking for a
预订数据库的种类
restaurant you know I don't want to get
你知道我不想去的餐厅
too deep into the domain model but we'll
对领域模型太过深入，但我们会
just work with it work in terms of
就用它来工作
bookings okay so first of all we need a
预订还可以，所以首先我们需要一个
booking entity go ahead and create that
预订实体继续创建
we're gonna probably need a
我们可能需要一个
configuration class right so we'll
配置类正确，所以我们将
create a configuration class for our
为我们创建一个配置类
application it's gonna be back by
应用程序将回来
database so we'll create a database
数据库，所以我们将创建一个数据库
repository a booking repository what
存放预订资料库
else do we need we need a controller we
否则我们需要控制器吗？
want a restful service to deal with this
想要一个宁静的服务来解决这个问题
so booking rest controller
所以预定休息控制器
and then it would be nice to have a web
然后拥有一个网络会很好
page as well so we'll go ahead and build
页面，所以我们继续进行构建
a a MVC controller let's see now
一个MVC控制器，让我们现在看看
so this is gonna be a JPA entity JP
所以这将成为JPA实体JP
application so I'm going to go ahead and
应用程序，所以我要继续
import the JP annotations here and we'll
在此处导入JP批注，我们将
just use it and you know IntelliJ to
只需使用它，您就会知道IntelliJ
kind of freeze through this as much as
通过这种冻结
possible then of course okay empty and
可能的话当然可以了
then we want this go ahead and go ahead
然后我们要继续前进
and generate the accessories and
并生成配件和
mutators controlled or command all able
变种人控制或命令所有能力
to get code formatting this is of course
获取代码格式这当然是
a primary key and they've generated new
一个主键，他们已经产生了新的
value so leave it like that
值，所以就这样
and then of course this is a custom
然后这当然是一个习惯
column so I'll leave it like this name
列，所以我将其保留为该名称
thank you validation this is a a rest
谢谢您的确认，这是一个休息
controller and as I mentioned before
控制器，就像我之前提到的
we're going to be using the spring floor
我们将使用弹簧地板
so we have a convenient annotation there
所以我们在那里有一个方便的注释
we want to be able to load all the
我们希望能够加载所有
bookings whenever somebody goes to a
每当有人去预订
restful endpoint so we'll create a
宁静的端点，因此我们将创建一个
endpoint that delivers a collection of
提供以下方面的集合的端点
bookings like that and right now we
这样的预订，现在我们
don't have a way to satisfy that
没有办法满足
requirement so we're just imported no
要求，所以我们只是导入否
add controller for the for the restful
为宁静添加控制器
you know it's an HTML page rather and
您知道这是一个HTML页面，并且
then we need to repository so here we
那么我们需要存储，所以在这里我们
actually take a man who's been called
实际带一个被称为
spring day during data which gives us
数据带来的春季
the ability to do finders you know based
进行您认识的发现者的能力
on convention and destroy an example say
约定并销毁示例说
extends JP a repository I'm gonna go
扩展JP我要去的存储库
ahead and say that we want to go to JP a
继续说我们要去JP a
repository for entities of type booking
类型预订实体的存储库
with an ID of type long and I can do
ID类型为long的我可以
anything here I can actually creates
我实际上可以在这里创建的任何东西
like a list of looking objects by name
就像按名称查找对象的列表
string name I can say you know here's my
字符串名称，我可以说你知道这是我的
query is gonna you know the query is
查询会知道
gonna be generated by convention
将由惯例产生
looking at this method named spring
看这个叫spring的方法
data's gonna say oh you want a query
数据会说哦，你想查询
that finds bookings by name and of
通过名称和名称查找预订
course behind the scenes that'll get
当然会在幕后
transition to something like you know
过渡到你知道的东西
okay
好的
etc okay that's very convenient we don't
等等，这很方便，我们不
need to worry too much about that and
不必为此担心太多
then of course to configure all this we
然后当然要配置所有这些
need to you know we need to turn on as a
您需要知道我们需要以
few features that screen boot has an
屏幕启动具有的一些功能
audio turn-on for us so first off look
音频为我们开启，所以先看一下
at a empty configuration class right now
现在在一个空的配置类中
on when I turn on transaction and we're
当我开启交易时，我们
going to turn on spring data web support
即将开启Spring Data Web支持
and then that is it better actually I
然后那实际上更好
have any beans to configure per se in
有任何可配置的bean
this application because spring boot
这个应用程序是因为spring boot
will do so much of it for us let's go
会为我们做很多事情
ahead and sketch out the pieces here
向前并在这里勾勒出碎片
this is going to be a controller a
这将是一个控制器
restful controller for our bookings and
宁静的控制器，用于我们的预订和
in order to make it work we're gonna
为了使它起作用，我们要
inject a or Auto wire in this case a
在这种情况下，注入或自动导线
reference to our booking repository here
参考我们的预订资料库
I say this died looking in that
我说这死在那
repository find all wallah and then what
仓库找到所有的wallah，然后是什么
else do we need let's test I think that
否则我们需要测试我认为
should be a good start but we probably
应该是一个好的开始，但我们可能
need something to actually insert data
需要一些东西来实际插入数据
for us so we'll go again we're gonna
为了我们，我们会再去的
rely on the fact that spring boot needs
依靠弹簧靴需要的事实
convention and it can work let's just
约定，它可以正常工作
convention so I want to create a new
约定，所以我想创建一个新的
directory here called the source main
此目录称为源主目录
resources like so and we'll tell
这样的资源，我们会告诉
IntelliJ to please go ahead and just be
IntelliJ请继续前进
aware of that new directory and spring
知道那个新目录和春天
to spring but--look by default for a
春天来了-但默认情况下寻找
file called application that properties
该文件称为应用程序的属性
of course you can support other property
当然你可以支持其他财产
files just like you normally would by
文件就像通常一样
using the add property source annotation
使用添加属性源注释
or you know the context the property
或者您知道属性的上下文
placeholder resolution making some in
占位符解析使
XML so here's the property I'll and
XML，这是我要的属性
we'll look at that in a bit and then
我们待会儿再看
right now we also want to load data or
现在我们还想加载数据或
application so load sequel in particular
应用程序，因此特别是负载续集
you know
你懂
each time the application is running so
每次应用程序运行时
I'm gonna go ahead and use my little
我要去用我的小东西
cheat sheet here just to say it's a good
备忘单只是说这很好
time like so go ahead and change you
像这样的时间来改变你
know we need that of course I don't know
知道我们需要那个，我当然不知道
just that's fine
没关系
okay so we'll we'll leave it like that
好吧，我们就这样离开它
when spring spring mood starts up it'll
当春天春天的心情开始时
see the data that's equal it'll see that
看到相等的数据，它将看到
we've configured in database or that we
我们已经在数据库中配置了
want to be you know talk to a database
想成为您知道与数据库对话
it'll also see that we've got the h2
它也会看到我们有H2
libraries on the class map for example
例如，类图上的库
and it'll give us an embedded database
它将为我们提供一个嵌入式数据库
if we don't provide one by ourselves so
如果我们不自己提供一个
if I go back down here and I configure a
如果我回到这里并配置一个
you know being of pie potato sorts then
你知道那是马铃薯派
it won't create one for me but since I
它不会为我创造一个，但是因为我
haven't it'll just assume I want an
只是假设我想要一个
embed one since it's got certain
嵌入一​​个，因为它可以确定
libraries on the craft path which is
工艺路线上的图书馆是
very smart that's very convenient it
很聪明，很方便
does what I need but you know it doesn't
做我需要的，但是你知道不需要
get my way if I want to do something
如果我想做某事，请顺路
different
不同
okay so dative stuffs equals loaded the
好吧，所以导语等于加载了
application components are here we'll
应用程序组件在这里，我们将
come back to this guy in a second and
一秒钟后回到这个家伙，
think that's a good start so right click
认为这是一个好的开始，所以右键单击
on this choose one as a application wait
在此选择一个作为应用程序等待
for this to go again yeah not at enable
为此再次进行，是的，不启用
auto configuration is where all the
自动配置是所有
magic is happening right so this is
魔术正在发生，所以这是
actually just so it's gonna look at the
其实只是要看一下
application it's gonna look at the
应用程序，它将在
components that are registered an
已注册的组件
application and realize oh this is a web
应用并意识到哦，这是一个网站
application we should probably go ahead
应用程序，我们应该继续
and start a tomcat for us you know so
并为我们创建一个tomcat
that they can get all quicker so
他们可以更快地得到所有
localhost like so should get you those
像这样的本地主机应该让你那些
four different end points
四个不同的终点
that's just rest of course nothing
那当然就是休息了
special again all that data all the JPA
再次将所有这些数据全部转换为JPA
support is provided by spring data we
弹簧数据提供了我们的支持
didn't have to write much color at all
根本不需要写很多颜色
for that and of course since its spring
为此，当然，因为它的春天
we're trying to help you be production
我们正在努力帮助您实现生产
ready you can do even get access to the
准备好您甚至可以访问
rest of the applications for example env
其他应用程序，例如env
employed air comes out of the box just
受雇的空气开箱即用
by having that spring booth starter
有了那个春天的摊位首发
actuator library in the classpath health
执行器库在classpath运行状况中
is that convenient for developers who
这样方便开发人员
want a you know a look at what's going
想要你知道发生了什么
on and so for example I actually have an
等等，例如，我实际上有一个
error my code here my sequel we can see
我在这里看到我的续集错误我的代码
that that's been reported
据报道
good to know very good to know what hey
很高兴知道非常高兴
where did I screw it up anyway come back
反正我在哪里弄回来的
to that and then of course you get
到那个，然后你当然会得到
things like beans which shows you all
像豆这样的东西可以向大家展示
the beans you know application context
您知道应用程序上下文的bean
you get things like metrics it shows you
您会看到指标向您显示的信息
how many requests have been made to it
向它提出了多少个请求
you know different end points and and
您知道不同的终点，并且
also more relevant the status codes of
也更相关的状态码
those different end points so I've made
那些不同的终点，所以我做了
one call to the env endpoint that had a
到具有一个
responsive status code 200 etc so all
响应状态码200等
this stuff you get just for free you
这些东西你只是免费获得的
know we haven't done a lot of code at
知道我们并没有做很多代码
all to get this working but we can do
所有人都可以做到这一点，但我们可以做到
better I mean let's go ahead and take a
更好，我的意思是让我们继续
look at what it means to you know work
看看对你了解工作意味着什么
from you know HTML page to turn it to
从您知道的HTML页面将其转到
render an HTML page again based on
根据以下内容再次呈现HTML页面
convention spring boot expects templates
约定Spring Boot需要模板
to be inside of the templates directory
放在模板目录中
but we need to we can choose different
但是我们需要选择不同的
styles for templates I'm gonna go ahead
我要继续的模板样式
and use time leaf type in each is a very
并在每个使用时间叶类型是非常
very powerful library for doing you know
您知道的非常强大的库
html5 natural templates that are very
html5非常自然的模板
similar in style to those of the wicked
与恶人的风格相似
or type histories templates etc or
或输入历史记录模板等或
facelets sort of from JSF although
虽然来自JSF，
that's a bit of a stretch so I'll go
有点麻烦，所以我去
ahead and add that dependency here very
向前，并在此添加该依赖性
convenient to do I can use intelligence
方便我可以运用智力
marble is the maven support here so you
大理石是这里的专家支持，所以您
can see all the different options I have
可以看到我拥有的所有不同选项
available it's already it's a transitive
可用，已经是可传递的
in dependency that's in dependency
在依赖中
management from the spring boot start up
从春季启动启动管理
parents all I got to do is import it I
父母，我要做的就是导入我
don't have to specify the version in
不必在中指定版本
this case and then once I've done that
这种情况下，然后一旦我做到了
spring boot has everything it needs to
弹簧靴具有所需的一切
automatically configure the engine for
自动配置引擎
me and know to look in the templates
我，知道去看模板
folder for for templates that we want to
我们想要的模板的文件夹
use to render stuff I'm gonna go ahead
用于渲染我要继续的东西
and just use this template here so we're
然后在这里使用这个模板
gonna call this one bookings it's just
会叫这个预订只是
gonna be numerate
会计算
the bookings we have nothing fancy here
我们这里的预订没有什么花哨的
just a very basic time league template
只是一个非常基本的时间联赛模板
you can see it's got a div element which
您可以看到它有一个div元素
has a special time leaf th namespace and
有一个特殊的时间名称空间
I can use the special syntax booking of
我可以使用特殊的语法预订
book
书
you know and then ready to talk it's
你知道然后准备谈论它
were to open this up in something like
会用类似的方式打开它
Dreamweaver you know an HTML editor
Dreamweaver您知道HTML编辑器
you'd actually get a reasonable
你实际上会得到一个合理的
facsimile of what's happening this is
传真这是怎么回事
just dummy text this won't actually be
只是虚拟文本，这实际上不是
rendered at runtime again that makes it
再次在运行时呈现它
a natural fit for for the innovation
天生适合创新
here and IntelliJ but also in things
在这里和IntelliJ但在事物上
like where's the web store I mean the
就像网上商店在哪里
awesome you know factored out type
你知道的很棒的类型
application you look to it and see what
您期待它的应用程序，看看有什么
else the last thing we want is to reload
否则，我们想要的最后一件事就是重新加载
our templates so we're gonna go ahead
我们的模板，以便我们继续
and just use a properties file and tell
并使用属性文件告诉
spring that we want to go ahead and not
春天，我们要继续前进，而不是
cache the templates so that woman when
缓存模板，以便女人在
we're doing development or just reload
我们正在开发或只是重新加载
and reload for us that way we don't have
并以这种方式为我们重新加载
to wait you know each time have to
等你知道每次
reboot just to update the template so
重启只是为了更新模板，所以
I'll go ahead and it stopped and the
我继续前进，它停止了，
last thing we need here of course is
我们当然需要的最后一件事是
actually an MVC controller for our
实际上是我们的MVC控制器
endpoint so again here we'll just use
端点，所以在这里我们只使用
the token apposite or create a request
令牌合适或创建请求
mapping an HTML page
映射HTML页面
you know string obviously please it's
你知道字符串明显吗
very important go ahead and use a string
非常重要，请继续使用字符串
am using model go ahead add an after bit
我正在使用模型继续添加后
or to carry and again my default it's
或再次携带我的默认值
just gonna look for the view named after
只是要寻找以名字命名的视图
this you know named in the same way or
你知道用同样的方式命名或
based on convention as the string that
基于约定作为字符串
we returned from this controller method
我们从这个控制器方法返回
so this will have the this will render
所以这将有这将呈现
an HTML page and delegate to this time
一个HTML页面并委托到这个时候
leaf template that we have here and the
我们在这里有叶子模板
restful controller just renders the
宁静的控制器只是呈现
collection and the objects directly
集合和对象直接
using JSON since our client expesive I
自从我们的客户使用JSON以来我就使用JSON
as an exception with JSON minute we can
作为JSON分钟的例外，我们可以
now relaunch
现在重新启动
or debug of course this is after all
或调试当然这毕竟是
just a regular Java program and we're
只是一个普通的Java程序，我们
just doing everything inside of the
只是在做所有的事情
editor here there's no reason to sort of
编辑在这里没有理由
conceptually move away if we had
从概念上讲，如果我们有
actually specify a data source there's
实际指定一个数据源
great tooling inside of the IntelliJ for
IntelliJ内部的出色工具
connecting sequel database and
连接续集数据库和
manipulating everything into not
操纵一切而不是
complete there and even inside of our
在那里完成，甚至在我们内部
HTML we could have used all of the
HTML，我们本可以使用所有
intelligence really great CSS and
智力真的很棒CSS
JavaScript support for example web jars
JavaScript支持，例如Web jars
is a way of bringing in jars nice week
是一种在罐子里度过美好的一周的方式
and there's nothing sweeter than a
没有比这更甜的了
really good tool that knows about
真正了解的好工具
JavaScript and knows about how to react
JavaScript并且知道如何做出反应
to things like JavaScript and CSS so
像JavaScript和CSS这样的东西
okay our application of course is backup
好吧，我们的应用程序当然是备份
bookings still works the way we expected
预订仍按我们预期的方式进行
to but now we can go to to the HTML
到，但现在我们可以转到HTML
endpoint and get the same data back in
端点并返回相同的数据
nichd ml um again this has all just been
再一次，这只是
code I haven't really haven't needed to
我真的不需要的代码
worry about anything else I mean I've
担心我想说的其他事情
put everything in one class they're just
把所有东西都放在一类
for convenience right but um it's also
为了方便起见，但是它也是
because it's very approachable I mean
因为这很平易近人
you're really have to there's not a lot
你真的必须有很多
of concerns to think about here right
考虑到这里的担忧
this is all just sort of the application
这全都是应用程序
you'd write in a pack of napkin and in
你会写在一包餐巾纸里
this case is it practically woman who's
这个案例实际上是女人
even in that shape you know one last
即使是那样的形状，你也知道最后一个
thing any of course is you can also
事情当然是你也可以
build right now this is config
现在建立这是配置
configured to create an uber jar so if
配置为创建一个超级罐子，所以如果
you build this application as is with
您按原样构建此应用程序
maven you'll get a a new bird drawer
行家，你会得到一个新的小鸟抽屉
which you can then Java jar and then run
然后您可以使用Java jar然后运行
on any container including in the cloud
在包括云在内的任何容器上
example on our open source platform as a
在我们的开源平台上的示例
service like Heroku et cetera but you
像Heroku et cetera这样的服务，但是您
might just as easily deploy it into a
可能同样容易地将其部署到
server container so in order to do that
服务器容器，以便这样做
you extend the spring boots from the
您将弹簧靴从
initializer and then you can override
初始化程序，然后您可以覆盖
the configure method here and again just
一次又一次地配置方法
go ahead and specify that class and then
继续并指定该课程，然后
finally
最后
our build here we don't need the jar and
我们在这里建立我们不需要罐子和
more we can say we wanted a jar a wall
我们可以说我们想要一个罐子在墙上
I'd rather write said you stalking
我宁愿写信说你缠扰
clearly to fit to the finish line there
显然适合终点线
and is able to plug in did one maybe
并可以插入一个也许
even it will just do everything's happy
即使一切都会幸福
and then we'll see it you know that's at
然后我们会看到它，您知道那是在
the application is now it's easily
该应用程序现在很容易
deployed so I can go ahead and a new
部署，这样我就可以继续
configuration it add new Tomcat server
配置它添加新的Tomcat服务器
local I've already got a tomcat oh four
我已经有一只雄猫了哦四
seven specified locally so I'll go ahead
在本地指定了七个，所以我继续
and specify all that and then we specify
并指定所有内容，然后我们指定
that I want to deploy a my my
我想部署我的我的
applications exploded by the way which
应用爆炸的方式
is great because you can always just
很棒，因为你总是可以
command f9 and control of nine and get
命令f9并控制9并获取
all the things updated as you know and
如您所知，所有事物都会更新
then there we go will you stop the run
然后我们走了，你会停止跑步吗
one and start the web application
一并启动Web应用程序
through Tomcat proper and of course this
通过适当的Tomcat，当然这
works just fine any other you know this
可以正常工作，任何其他你知道的
is a lightweight servlet container like
是一个轻量级的servlet容器，例如
like jetty
像码头
it also looks fine in more traditional
在更传统的情况下看起来也不错
applications never lose like the
应用程序永远不会像
WebSphere and so on and then stay Boston
WebSphere等，然后留在波士顿
whatever you want right so there's the
随便你怎么想
actual application that working for them
为他们工作的实际应用
from Tomcat of course the Tomcat works
从Tomcat当然可以使用Tomcat
fine inside of IntelliJ everything else
可以在IntelliJ里面很好
seems to work great in terminology and
似乎在术语上效果很好，
new in the in the latest version of
最新版本中的新功能
course is one of my favorite need you
当然是我最喜欢的需求之一
know the relevance is the five hundred
知道相关性是五百
support so if we had more time I could
支持，所以如果我们有更多时间我可以
just click create this sign in its and
只需单击在其中创建此标志，然后
then deploy but I'll just need to your
然后部署，但我只需要
imagination you can get this entire
想象力，你可以得到整个
application working rest working web
应用程序工作其余工作网站
application that's it there and then
在那里的应用程序，然后
deploy to production all within you know
在您所知的范围内全部部署到生产
five minutes of every 10 minutes on in
每十分钟五分钟
webinar time not bad I think and I think
网络研讨会的时间还不错，我认为，我认为
it's because this editor makes it so
这是因为该编辑器使它如此
easy to get just kind of work through
容易完成工作
code you know you don't have to worry
您知道的代码不必担心
about the nonsense and frames of course
关于废话和框架
moans making it easy to get through the
ans吟使人容易通过
night attach okay so you're on thank God
晚上好吧，所以你继续感谢上帝
okay video was very very interesting and
好的视频非常非常有趣，
okay we are but short on time now
好吧，我们现在时间很短
I will rush through the last remaining
我会匆匆完成剩下的
items I want to show in IntelliJ so just
我想在IntelliJ中显示的项目
try record no no problem we have ok here
尝试记录没有问题，我们可以在这里
and I'll stay later we can stay after
我待会再来
the webinar take questions of course
网络研讨会当然会提问题
right yes of course well so we have a
对，当然可以，所以我们有一个
couple of new inspections for xml
几个新的xml检查
configuration files which will highlight
配置文件将突出显示
superfluous or yeah just redundant
是多余的，还是多余的
configurations as well as wrong
配置以及错误
configuration when you for example mix
配置时，例如混合
factory and and class instantiation we
工厂和类实例化我们
have of course auto bio ring inspections
当然有自动生物环检查
so that's one here's correct although
所以这是正确的
it's never used so that's why it's
它从未被使用过，所以这就是为什么
growing but this one here we have two
越来越多，但是这里有两个
candidates so what I can do is add a
候选人，所以我能做的就是添加一个
qualifier and I'll just tell which one I
限定词，我只告诉我一个
want to use and of course I can navigate
想使用，当然我可以导航
Whitacre again and you know a couple of
Whitacre又来了，你知道几个
other things for all the wiring have
所有布线的其他东西
been improved as well and one thing
也得到了改善，一件事
which is very nicely improved in
这是非常好的改进
IntelliJ 13 as better messages for
IntelliJ 13作为更好的消息
constructor mismatch so if you have
构造函数不匹配，所以如果您有
constructor ask configuration in your
构造函数询问您的配置
being and they don't match the actual
存在，他们与实际不符
constructor you are attempting to use
您尝试使用的构造函数
you will get a very detailed information
您将获得非常详细的信息
more what is wrong and what needs to be
还有什么是错误的，什么是必须的
changed
变了
okay so much for highlighting
还可以突出显示
improvements and now to one a very big
改进，现在已经很大
feature in IntelliJ 13 which is the new
IntelliJ 13中的新增功能
spring tool window which we haven't
我们还没有的弹簧工具窗口
shown yet so what does it do and it
显示了，所以它是做什么的和它
gives you a very good navigation and
给您一个很好的导航
ability to not only see your modules
不仅可以看到您的模块的能力
here in the first column and the second
在第一列和第二列
column we shown if I set switch
如果设置了开关，我们将显示该列
reconfigured in the spring facet as well
在弹簧方面也进行了重新配置
as the corresponding spring
作为相应的春天
configuration files it's on our
配置文件在我们的
application files
申请文件
code files and here we have bullets of
代码文件，这里有
reciting beans as well as the
背诵豆子以及
documentation window so you can easily
文档窗口，因此您可以轻松
scroll to your application see all the
滚动到您的应用程序，查看所有
beans at once see what they are about
豆子立刻知道它们的含义
get all the documentation all in one
将所有文档全部集中在一起
place so that's very convenient if you
的地方，所以如果你很方便
are searching for Sunbeam or for some
正在寻找新光或一些
configuration problem in your spring
你春天的配置问题
application another very neat feature is
应用程序另一个非常整洁的功能是
enabling the graph so it will show a
启用图表，以便显示
small graph we know under the
我们知道的小图
documentation or can also disable the
文档或也可以禁用
documentation so you see it directly
文档，以便您直接查看
relationships of the currently selected
当前选择的关系
beam you can also navigate to the beams
您也可以导航至横梁
respectable clicking would to its item
值得点击的项目
in the list and there's a couple of
在列表中，有几个
other navigation and filtering
其他导航和过滤
possibilities as well so it's very
可能性也很大
powerful the next thing
强大的下一件事
is about spring MVC support we have
关于我们对Spring MVC的支持
worked on improving the documentation
致力于改善文档
possibilities as well there so we have a
还有可能性，所以我们有一个
very basic request mapping here and I'm
非常基本的请求映射在这里，我
just now going to switch to the embassy
刚要去大使馆
tab which is of course also new in
标签，这当然也是新的
IntelliJ 13 and here you will have the
IntelliJ 13，在这里您将拥有
list of all URLs as well as the
所有网址的列表以及
controller's so it's my request mapping
控制器的，这就是我的请求映射
and here we can actually see the
在这里我们实际上可以看到
documentation for the request mapping as
请求映射的文档为
well and I've prepared a bit more
好，我准备了更多
complicated controller here which has a
这里有一个复杂的控制器
couple of more annotations and
几个更多的注释和
parameters as well and they will also be
参数，它们也将是
shown in the documentation window so you
显示在文档窗口中，以便您
can actually see the path variables as
可以实际看到路径变量为
well as the types and you see the aged
以及类型，您会看到老年人
HTTP methods which are a little bit just
HTTP方法只是一点点
yes mapping much more yeah that's really
是的，映射更多，是的，这真的
amazing a lot of people you know it
让很多人都知道
seems like some people want to be able
好像有些人想要
to use and configure everything with
使用和配置一切
spring um you see one central place and
春天，你看到一个中心地方，
others want to be able to use the
其他人希望能够使用
annotations but then they risk having
注释，但是他们冒着拥有
their their mappings and the route
他们的地图和路线
spread across circ and controllers now
现在遍布中国保监会和管制员
with this you can have both you can have
有了这个，你可以同时拥有
your convenient you know code next to
您方便，您知道旁边的代码
your endpoints and configuration next
您的端点和配置
and points and then still get the
和点，然后仍然得到
bird's-eye view
鸟瞰
you know your application controllers
你知道你的应用程序控制器
that's really great this documentation
这个文档真的很棒
is also available from any other place
也可以从任何其他地方获得
from the IDE so when I have Auto
从IDE，所以当我有自动
completion here to some URL I can also
在这里完成一些URL我也可以
invoke the documentation here and see at
在此处调用文档并在
a glance what parameters I need to pass
一目了然我需要传递什么参数
in if it's a gas emitters or the post
在它是一个气体排放者或邮政
method request mapping everything else
方法请求映射其他所有内容
so that's very convenient to navigate
所以导航非常方便
apropos invocation we also have just
apropos调用我们也有
small little icon here which allows us
这里的小图标
to actually navigate 2d related view of
实际浏览2D的相关视图
D request mapping so you can just click
D请求映射，因此您只需单击
you go to the corresponding view of
你去对应的视图
course we also resolve any model
当然我们也可以解决任何模型
properties here as you can see
可以看到这里的属性
refactoring of course floats across
当然重构过程
everything so I think that's a very nice
一切，所以我认为这非常好
petition to have the documentation and
请愿以备有文件和
the navigation from the spring MVC
从春季MVC导航
wouldn't know for your web applications
不知道您的Web应用程序
and then we have two other topics which
然后我们还有另外两个主题
I'm just going to tell you without
我只想告诉你
showing stampers we no support the add
显示压模我们不支持添加
context hierarchy annotation for test
用于测试的上下文层次结构注释
contexts and we also finally support
上下文，我们也最终支持
MongoDB as well as new 4G and jump
MongoDB以及新的4G和跳跃
higher and repository annotations as
更高版本和存储库注释为
well as two corresponding XML
以及两个对应的XML
configuration text from their namespaces
来自其名称空间的配置文本
so we are to date in this area as well
所以我们也要在这方面
no ok that's all we could fit in this
不，这就是我们所能满足的
small one our webcast so we are coming
我们的网络广播很小，所以我们来了
to the conclusion now and just very easy
现在得出结论，非常容易
yeah we have some we have some nice
是的，我们有一些，我们有一些不错的
stuff to announce so what's coming in
要宣布的东西，所以会发生什么
IntelliJ 13 dot point releases for
IntelliJ 13点发布
spring support we are going to publish
我们将要发布的春季支持
actually a spring open API for
实际上是针对
third-party packing developers so if you
第三方包装开发商，如果您
are planning to support your own XML or
正在计划支持您自己的XML或
Java context annotations for any spring
任何春季的Java上下文注释
plug-in for example or for your own home
例如插件或您自己的家
build a spring frame that you will be
建立一个弹簧框架，你将成为
able to do it using this open API and of
能够使用此开放式API和
course we expect our plugin developers
当然，我们希望我们的插件开发人员
to step in and maybe develop some more
介入并可能发展更多
plugins for the spring support in
春季支持插件
IntelliJ for lesser-known spring sub
IntelliJ用于鲜为人知的Spring Sub
projects and for 13.1 support we are
项目和13.1支持，我们是
going to work very hard on near spring
在春天附近要非常努力地工作
and missie support we
和小姐支持我们
work on the at enable of that industry
致力于该行业的发展
as well as Java config for Java conflict
以及针对Java冲突的Java配置
support for spring MVC applications and
支持spring MVC应用程序和
of course we will update with the latest
当然，我们会更新最新的
Weald releases of all the springs
所有弹簧的恶性释放
approach it's already support and
接近已经支持的方法
Croatian security and so on and so on so
克罗地亚安全等等，依此类推
yeah I think it's going to be
是的，我认为这将会是
interesting especially we'll see
有趣，特别是我们会看到
upcoming spring photo release in two
即将发布的春季照片分为两部分
days I think and yeah that's all for me
天，我想，对，这就是我的全部
so that's amazing man
所以那个很棒的人
this was fun thanks for having me yeah
这很有趣，谢谢有我
thanks jinyoung and thank everyone for
谢谢jinyoung并感谢大家
attending and make sure to visit our
参加并确保参观我们的
website and download the latest version
网站并下载最新版本
of IntelliJ IDEA as well as go to spring
IntelliJ IDEA以及春季
dot IO website to find all the guides
dot IO网站查找所有指南
how to get started with spring and of
如何从春季开始
course who was in Twitter so you get all
当然是谁在Twitter上，所以您可以全部获得
the news absolutely yeah and one more
这个新闻绝对是的，还有更多
section is I think we have enough time
我觉得我们有足够的时间
to go through the list of all the
浏览所有的清单
questions and articles I'm I'm looking
我正在寻找的问题和文章
at some of them now too
现在也有一些
one question was can you show how to
一个问题是你能表明如何
migrate to a full-blown war of course we
迁移到一场全面战争
didn't answered that do you have any do
没有回答你有事吗
you see any questions there I guess I
你在那里看到任何问题我想我
just already shown how to be great dog
刚刚已经展示了如何成为伟大的狗
to war yep the spring good app by the
战争是由春天的好应用程序
way I'm STAAR buicks a man on Twitter
我是STAAR的方式是在Twitter上吸引男人
find me there and John is the same as
在那找到我，约翰和
his name but without space any details
他的名字，但没有空格
on when it closes support she's coming
当它关闭时，她就要来了
in spring cool I don't know if we have
在春季凉爽的时候，我不知道我们是否有
been closer support specifically
更加密切地支持
specific specifically planned but after
具体计划，但之后
all it is it is just a bunch of JVM
就是一堆JVM
types at in the day so even if we don't
在一天中键入，即使我们不
have a specific idiomatic integration
有特定的习惯用法整合
you can still use it from from closure
您仍然可以从关闭使用它
obviously it would be cool to see a
显然，看到一个
moralist be taken certain things one
道德主义者被当成一件事情
more question
更多问题
it asks if if you have wasn't one being
它询问您是否不是一个人
much too is a outward outward in
外向内向外
dependency injection so its highlight it
依赖注入，因此突出了它
as a red wine in the IDE one of these
作为IDE中的红酒之一
beans is used for test purposes so how
豆用于测试目的，如何
to handle this yeah would you mind
处理这个是的，你介意吗
answering this question personally i R
我亲自回答这个问题
is it another softer question so I if
这是另一个更柔和的问题吗，如果
you use more than one beam which which
您使用多个光束
the dependency injection and injection
依赖注入和注入
highlight visa red yeah there can be a
突出显示签证红色，可以
multiple reasons for that so one reason
有多种原因，所以一个原因
which is very common as just some miss
这很常见，只是有些想念
configuration of the spring facet so
弹簧小平面的配置如此
that's the first issue to check if the
这是检查是否
spring configuration setup in your IIE
IIE中的spring配置设置
resembles what your application actually
类似于您的应用程序实际
should do if that doesn't solve the term
如果那不能解决这个问题应该做
please file a back with more information
请向后退以提供更多信息
and we will take a look at that so it's
我们来看一下，所以
how to answer this versus alter a
如何回答这个与改变
specific context sorry Jung the question
具体情况对不起荣格这个问题
was if one of these beans here is used
如果使用这里的一种豆子
for tests only so personally I give you
仅用于个人测试我给你
could use profiles and okay ohayo so
可以使用个人资料，好吧，所以
there they correctly highlight
他们在那里正确地突出显示
dependencies
依存关系
okay so the the configuration for test
好的，所以测试的配置
contexts which are used for example for
例如用于的上下文
integration tests um it's usually
集成测试，通常
separated from the production context so
与生产环境分开，所以
you don't need actually to configure
您实际上不需要进行配置
anything and you Springfest it for the
任何东西，你Springfest它的
tests context because it will
测试上下文，因为它将
automatically pick up and everything
自动拿起一切
from the code so if you have maybe
从代码，所以如果你有可能
configured some manual context you
配置了一些手动上下文
should delete it and try again if it
应该删除它，然后再试一次
works now if it doesn't and please
如果没有，现在可以工作，请
follow back again I will specific code
再次返回我将具体代码
examples and we will investigate one
例子，我们将调查一个
more question so Peter asks if we have
还有更多问题，所以彼得问我们是否
the s'more two window for Joey yes we do
乔伊的s'more两个窗口是的
and it's named Java Enterprise so if you
它的名字叫Java Enterprise，所以如果您
open any Java EE project you'll find it
打开任何Java EE项目，您都会找到它
cool
凉
one more question on spring profile
关于弹簧轮廓的另一个问题
annotation cool asks if any if there are
批注很酷，问是否有
any improvements or trim profile support
任何改进或修剪轮廓支持
I guess if you find something broken
我想你是否发现一些坏东西
with that you should the complete report
这样你应该完整的报告
it because it's supposed to work out is
因为它应该解决的
okay to our questions about the spring
好的，关于春天的问题
and Missy support especially for the
和小姐的支持，特别是对于
past attribute from me yes it's the non
我的过去属性是非
missing link in our support and there's
我们的支持中缺少链接，
even a ticket for it if you can look it
连票都可以看
up in our dr. King system it's on the
在我们的博士中国王系统在
list of spring MVC improvements we are
我们是春季MVC改进的清单
planning for 13.1 for is the question
为13.1计划是问题
now to validate the apart attribute of
现在验证
the spring MVC custom text for trace
Spring MVC自定义文本进行跟踪
piece or s to navigate to D
件或s导航至D
corresponding baking beans for example
例如相应的烤豆
cool surprise you guys don't already
你们还没有惊喜
have that this stuff is easy yeah I
有这个东西很容易是的，我
guess really so great yeah what's the
猜得真是太好了，那是什么
next question I'm sorry one on Gretel
下一个问题对不起Gretel
support is is there any plans to provide
是否有提供任何计划的支持
rebels builds or examples on spring
叛军在春季建立或树立榜样
website I guess already some examples
我猜网站已经有一些例子
with griddle beautiful right yes so all
与煎锅美丽的权利是的，所以所有
of those guides that I mentioned that
我提到的那些指南中
spring that IO for - guides are
IO for-指导的春天
available both as Gradle and maven palms
可作为Gradle和Maven手掌使用
so every single one of them is and
所以他们每个人都是
wherever possible we use spring boots so
我们尽可能地使用弹簧靴
so have them in fact the guides feature
所以实际上有他们的指南功能
the Gradle build and then a link to the
Gradle构建，然后链接到
main one so Gail first actually and all
主要的，所以盖尔首先实际上和所有
of them I hope that helped is that Thank
我希望他们对他们有帮助，谢谢
You Man
你这个人
oh okay thank you very much for
哦，很好，非常感谢你
listening uh thanks to Josh again for
再次感谢乔希
joining us and showing us some
加入我们，向我们展示一些
impressive usages of spring in it blue
蓝色的春天令人印象深刻的用法
chain thank you I for showing me into
链谢谢你我带我进
impressive IntelliJ
令人印象深刻的IntelliJ
so every day
所以每天